<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Aufa Nabil</title>
    <link>https://chillytaka.github.io/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Aufa Nabil</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:09:08 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chillytaka.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Efisiensi</title>
      <link>https://chillytaka.github.io/projects/efisiensi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 10:09:08 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chillytaka.github.io/projects/efisiensi/</guid>
      <description>Efisiensi is an app for booking bus tickets accross Indonesia. It has many feature such as multiple tickets booking, self-select seats, see purchase history, easy boarding by only showing the app, and many more !.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart Chair</title>
      <link>https://chillytaka.github.io/projects/smart-chair/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 10:05:09 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chillytaka.github.io/projects/smart-chair/</guid>
      <description>A group project as one of the requirement to pass Telematics Project course. The SmartChair project is a chair with the ability to remind you if you have sitting for too long and it has a treatment mode to treat hemorrhoid by heating the sitting area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evolty 2020 Main Website</title>
      <link>https://chillytaka.github.io/projects/evolty-2020-main-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2019 08:56:30 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chillytaka.github.io/projects/evolty-2020-main-website/</guid>
      <description>EVOLTY is an annual event from Electric Engineering Faculy. I work on their main website, along with some additional functionalities such as general administration system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foculance</title>
      <link>https://chillytaka.github.io/projects/foculance/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 19:24:02 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chillytaka.github.io/projects/foculance/</guid>
      <description>Foculance is an app to control other apps or games by giving those apps a usage time limit for children. The intended usage is to monitor and children phone usage throughout the day with hassle free setup from parents. Foculance is able to achieved 3rd place on GEMASTIK XII category Softwawre Development on 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mage 5 Main Website</title>
      <link>https://chillytaka.github.io/projects/mage/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 08:16:33 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://chillytaka.github.io/projects/mage/</guid>
      <description>MAGE is an annual event from Computer Engineering degree at Sepuluh Nopember Institute of Technology. I work on their main website, along with some additional functionalities such as online test system and general administration system.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
